boonli.com 2018-08-19

# Boonli | Welcome - Privacy policy

## Privacy policy

The privacy of the consumers who use this site is of utmost importance to boonli.com. We respect your privacy and have instituted policies to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure and responsible manner. Personal information means any information that identifies you as an individual such as name, address, phone number, email address, credit card and bank account numbers.

For each person that visits our Web site and signs up to use our service, we collect your e-mail addresses, name and street address, telephone number, fax number. We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

boonli.com uses Comodo CA Limited SSL/TLS certificates, which provides 256-bit encryption to protect the personal information stored on our servers hosted in the Amazon Cloud (excluding credit card data which if saved, is secured with a Level 1 PCI Compliant Gateway).  Please go to [](http://mktg.boonli.com/security)[https://www.boonli.com/security](http://mktg.boonli.com/security) to view our payment processing security page.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. However, we may use information collected to customize the content and/or layout of our web pages. With respect to cookies, we store one temporary cookie in your browser while you are logged into the site. The cookie is deleted once you logout of boonli.com, or automatically is removed from your browser within 24 hours.

E-mail correspondence or periodic mailings to your postal address will only be sent if boonli.com has important information regarding your school lunch program or the operation of the services provided on our Web Site.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online and/or school meal related business.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to their own personal information [including proprietary information] that we maintain: unique identifier information (e.g., user ID), transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number, and a description of the type of information we maintain.

Consumers can access this information by viewing their User Profile that was created upon their initial registration.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in their contact information, unique identifiers, transaction information, and communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail to [**support@boonli.com**](mailto:support@boonli.com).

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, we can be reached via e-mail at [**support@boonli.com**](mailto:support@boonli.com), postal address at 820 American Street, San Carlos, CA 94070 or by telephone at 1-800-381-6511.
